《烈探雷徹》前情提要
Previously on Reacher...
我收到你的消息了
I got your message.
110特別調查組 “10-30” 這是求救信號
110th, 10-30. A distress call.
卡爾文弗朗茨被謀殺了
Calvin Franz was murdered.
如果他給你打過電話 那他可能也給隊里其他人打過
If he was calling you for help, he may have been trying to get in touch with the rest of the unit.
我給奧唐納 迪克森 桑切斯 和奧羅斯科打了電話 都沒人接
I called O'Donnell, Dixon, Sanchez and Orozco. No one's answering.
我買通了門房
I paid off the concierge.
他指認內格利登記入住
He I.D.'d Neagley as checking in.
盯緊那家酒店還有他們
Just keep an eye on that hotel and them.
- 沒人會知道你是誰 - 但你知道
No one will really know who you are. But you know.
- 嘿 奧唐納 - 嘿 內格利
Hey, O'Donnell. Hey, Neagley.
只是一個名單 所有名字的首字母都是AM
Just a list of names, all starting with the initials "A.M."
我剛得到的是一頁又一頁的隨機數據
I just got page after page of random numbers.
- 沒有順序 沒有意義 什么都沒 - 至少我們覺得沒有 而且暫時而已
No order, no meaning. Nothing. At least to us, for now.
你有什么想法
What are you thinking?
我覺得有人一心想干掉特別調查員
I'm thinking there's someone hell-bent on taking out the special investigators.
他們是沖我們來的
And they're coming after us.
很好
Good.
如果他們的目標是110小組 那他們怎么還沒殺我們
So, if someone's coming after the 110, how come they haven't made a run at the three of us yet?
你之前跟家人在樹林里 沒人能找到我
You were in the woods with your family, no one can ever find me
或許還沒輪到內格利
and maybe they just hadn't gotten around to Neagley yet.
他們去了我們的酒店房間
They were in our hotel rooms,
也許他們是想抓或者殺了我們 隨后因故不得不匆忙離開
maybe to grab us or take us out, but then had to bail for some reason.
我們得再試著警告其他人
We need to try again to warn the others.
- 我會給桑切斯和奧羅斯科打電話 - 我來聯系迪克森
I'll call Sanchez and Orozco. I got Dixon.
街對面幾棟房子外有一輛黑色轎車
There's a black sedan across the street, couple houses down.
跟昨天遇到的是同一輛
Same one as yesterday.
我猜你說得對 我們被跟蹤了
Guess you were right. We're being followed.
你打算怎么處理
How you want to play this?
我要去做個自我介紹
I'm gonna go introduce myself.
看看這個該死的美男子
Look at this fucking beaut.
他打算干什么呢
What's he think he's gonna do?
我他媽的鼻子 兄弟
Fucking nose, man.
有槍
Gun!
就像過去美好的時光
Just like the good old days.
是啊 你在一旁觀望 而我把所有工作都做完了
Yeah, you on the sidelines while I do all the work.
伙計們 這是他的槍
Uh, fellas, this was his gun.
紐約市警察局
NYPD?
名叫蓋塔諾拉索
Name's Gaitano Russo.
嘿 別看我 你把所有工作都做完了
Don't look at me. You did all the work.
我得說 兄弟 你闖大禍了
Got to say, man. Major screwup.
拉索一醒來 整個紐約市警察局都會追捕你
Soon as Russo wakes up, the entire NYPD's gonna be after your ass.
你為什么下手那么狠
Why'd you got to hit him so hard, huh?
我出手從不手軟
I don't hit soft.
- 襲警可是要坐很久的牢 - 那只狗的事情讓我很生氣
Well, a cop puncher's gonna do some serious time. I was pissed about the dog,
我以為他參與了殺害弗朗茨和斯旺
and I assumed he was involved in killing Franzy and Swan.
你怎么教我們的  “在調查中 假設害死人”
What did you teach us? "In an investigation, assumptions kill."
是“在調查時 細節至關重要”
No, it was "In an investigation, details matter".
我沒殺他 只是打斷了他的鼻子 他醒來時會沒事的
I didn't kill him, just broke his nose. He'll be fine when he wakes up.
糟了 蓋塔諾拉索
Shit. Gaitano Russo.
又叫蓋伊拉索 他是弗朗茨謀殺案的調查人員
Guy Russo. He's the investigating officer in Franz's homicide.
- 我在檔案中看到過他的名字 - 他是怎么開始跟蹤你的
I saw it in the files. And how'd he get on your tail?
紐約市警察局看到弗朗茨 給你打了電話 標記了你的名字
NYPD saw the calls Franz made to you, flagged your name,
你買票的時候 他們收到了提醒
got an alert when you bought the plane tickets,
自從你落地以后一直跟著你 問題是 為什么
been on you since you landed. Question is "why?"
問題是 哪里
Question is "where?"
哪里可以藏一個近兩米的重罪犯 這樣你就不會被關進監獄了
As in, where do we hide a six-foot-five felon so you don't wind up in the pokey.
我不走 這里是案發現場
I'm not leaving. The case is here.
也許不是
Maybe not.
我給桑切斯和奧羅斯科的辦公室 打電話時 語音信箱已經滿了
When I called Sanchez and Orozco's office, voice mail was full.
這是個噩兆
That's a bad sign.
考慮到這位“拳王” 擊倒了一位執法人員
So it might not be a bad time to get out of Dodge,
現在出去避風頭或許不失為好主意
considering Cocky Balboa here just knocked out a lawman.
好吧 我們去大西洋城
Fine. We'll head down to Atlantic City,
看我們能不能找到那些人
see if we can find the guys.
首先 我們要退房 并在拉索恢復知覺
First we got to check out of our hotel and find a more generic ride
讓警方“小心提防”你之前 找到更普通的交通工具
before Russo regains consciousness and puts out a BOLO.
路虎攬勝太顯眼了
Range Rover's too conspicuous.
就是因為你 我們才不能用好東西
You're the reason we can't have nice things.
烈探雷徹
第二季第二集
本WEB版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  雙語合并
等等 我不明白 是出車禍了嗎
Wait, I don't understand. Was it a car accident?
沒有 他就踹了一下車
No, he just kicked the car.
好吧 那為什么 安全氣囊都彈出來了
Well, then how the hell did the airbag go off?
他踹了一下車
He kicked the car,
然后把警察拉了出來 狠狠地揍了一頓
then he pulled the cop out and he knocked his dick in the dirt.
這家伙就是頭野獸
I'm telling you, this guy's a beast.
到時候 我需要支援
When the time comes, I'm gonna need some backup.
會給你安排支援的
And you'll get it.
但現在 你繼續跟蹤監視他們 別搞砸了
But for now, you just stay on their asses, and don't fuck this up.
明白
Understood.
機場臨時停車僅在一號停車場
Short-term airport parking only in Lot 1.
特里蒙特有輛2019款雅閣 正在出售 價格低于市場價
There's a 2019 Accord for sale up in Tremont for way under market value.
僅限現金交易
Cash-only deal.
布朗克斯區最常被盜的車型之一 他不想要任何文件嗎
One of the most stolen makes and models for sale in the Bronx, and the guy wants no paperwork?
我們坐進去 就跟火燒屁股一樣
We sit in that thing, we burn our asses.
我們別無選擇 我們被警方標記了 什么都租不了
We don't have a choice. We're flagged in the system. We can't rent anything under our names.
我們開著偷來的車到處走 那很有可能被逮捕
Well, we drive around in a stolen vehicle, we risk getting pinched.
我有解決辦法了
I've got our solution.
你的臥底工作怎么樣了
How was your undercover job?
雷徹
Reacher.
你怎么知道我在臥底
How'd you know I was undercover?
考慮到當時的情況 你會馬上過來
Considering the circumstances, you would've come right away.
但你沒有 這意味著 你最近才收到我們的消息
But you didn't, which can only mean you didn't get our messages until recently.
如果你在休假 你會向你的辦公室匯報
But if you were on vacation, you would've checked in with your office periodically.
所以你一定是去做臥底了 還藏得很深
So you had to be working undercover, deep undercover,
沒辦法頻繁簽到
where frequent check-ins aren't always possible.
你還是一如既往地厲害啊
Same old Reacher.
我在調查一起企業貪污案
Corporate embezzlement case.
在德克薩斯州待了很久
Stuck in Texas so long, I started to think
久到我都開始覺得自己 喜歡牛仔靴和高中橄欖球了
I actually liked cowboy boots and high school football.
你還帶著假身份證嗎
Still got your fake ID with you?
- 帶著呢 - 很好
- Yeah. - Good.
- 拿它去租車吧 - 為什么要保密
Use it to rent the car. What's with all the secrecy?
內格利 奧唐納和我被警方標記了
Neagley, O'Donnell and I have been flagged in the system.
我還打暈了一名警察
And I punched out a cop.
好吧 并不意外
Of course you did.
那么
So...
弗朗茨...
Franz.
是的
Yeah.
斯旺也兇多吉少
And Swan, most likely.
桑切斯和奧羅斯科也失蹤了
Sanchez and Orozco are MIA, too.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 那我們來調查吧
Okay, so we take care of business.
不要惹特別調查員
You do not mess with the special investigators.
接下來
Next.
- 一定要租一輛... - SUV 我知道 你需要車內空間高點
Make sure you get an... SUV. I know. You need the headroom.
太好了 很高興看到你還在這里
Good. Glad to see you're still here.
感覺我永遠都不會離開
Feel like I'm never gonna leave.
如果世界上任何一個 軍事基地報告了任何違規行為
If it's reported at any Army base anywhere in the world,
無論多么輕微 我們都得處理
no matter how minor the infraction, we're copied on it.
你發現什么特別的事了嗎
Well, anything jump out at you?
是的 20分鐘前 有一只蜜露大小的老鼠
Yeah, a rat the size of a honeydew about 20 minutes ago.
說真的
- Seriously? - Yeah.
它又回到那堆箱子那邊了
It's back in those boxes somewhere.
好惡心
Gross.
說到老鼠 我覺得 我發現了一只可疑的“老鼠”
Well, speaking of rats, I think I smell one.
阿富汗的一名指揮官 認為有人在偷航空燃料
A commanding officer at a base in Afghanistan thinks someone's stealing aviation fuel.
把汽油抽走 然后再賣出去
Siphoning off gas to resell it on the side?
這不是軍方想讓我們優先處理的案子
Not exactly the kind of priority case the Army wants us taking on.
我覺得并不是有人在偷取并倒賣燃料
Right, but see, I don't think anybody's stealing and reselling anything.
看看這些數字 它們總能說明問題
Take a look at these numbers. They always tell a story.
我注意到每次基地里有燃料丟失時
See, I noticed that every time fuel went missing from the base,
都是在一趟特定的航班之后
it was always after a specific flight.
即每當C-17 將悍馬車運回美國的時候
Whenever C-17s ferried Humvees back home to the States.
我的意思是 這是個小細節 但在調查時 細節至關重要
I mean, it's a minor detail, but in an investigation, details matter.
我喜歡這句
I like that.
我會說這句的
I'm gonna use it.
我的就是你的
What's mine is yours.
那么
So...
你推測出來了嗎
you have a theory?
是的 沒有跡象表明基地附近
Yeah. There's been no indication of black market fuel sales
存在黑市燃料銷售的情況
anywhere on or around the base,
那這些燃料是怎么消失的呢
so how does all that fuel go missing?
讓燃料消失的最佳方式 就是把它燒了
Best way to make gas disappear is to burn it up.
沒錯 內格利有儲藏運輸石油的經驗
Exactly. Now, Neagley's got the bulk fuel experience
她認為所有運送悍馬的航班 都是故意過度加油的
and she thinks all the Humvee flights are intentionally being over-fueled.
但當這些飛機降落時
But, when those planes land,
油箱中的燃油量與預期相符
the amount of fuel in the tanks is exactly what's expected,
這些都被記錄到賬簿中了
and that gets logged into the books.
怎么會這樣
So, how does that happen?
多余的燃料是在飛機運輸不為人知的
The excess fuel is being used to transport more weight
- 額外貨物的過程中消耗掉的 - 對
than people realize is on the plane. Yeah.
運輸了一些沉重而秘密的東西
Something heavy and secret is being moved.
沒錯 悍馬車里有違禁品
Exactly. Contraband in the Humvees.
毒品 槍支 被盜現金 上述所有
Drugs, guns, stolen cash, all of the above.
干得好 迪克森
Good work, Dixon.
你找到了一起值得我們關注的案子
You just found a case worthy of our attention.
我不知道你的感覺 但這些調查讓我口干舌燥
I don't know about you, but all this sleuthing's made me thirsty.
想去慶祝一下嗎
Want to go celebrate?
你可以請我喝一杯
You can buy me a drink.
我得繼續處理這些報告
I got to keep working on these reports.
- 下次吧 - 好的
Maybe next time. Yeah.
但再說一次
But again,
- 干得好 迪克森 - 是啊
excellent work, Dixon. Yeah.
沒問題 如我所說 數字總能說明問題
No problem. Like I said, numbers always tell the story.
這些數字跟你說明問題了嗎
So, the numbers telling you a story?
是的 但這就像晦澀難懂的電影 完全無法理解
Yeah, and it's a David Lynch film. It's totally incomprehensible.
如果這些是分數 那寫下這些數字的人就太粗心了
I mean, if these are supposed to be fractions, then it's sloppy work.
有些沒被約分
Some of them aren't even reduced.
我也注意到了這一點
I noticed that, too.
也許這些數據代表數量
Maybe the numbers represent hard quantities.
比如 十分之八的某物 而不是五分之四的某物
Like, eight out of ten somethings, and not just four-fifths of something?
有可能
Maybe.
嗯 有可能 除此以外 還有兩件事很突出
Yeah, maybe. Beyond that, two things stick out.
這里面沒有百分之百 也就是說沒有九分之九
None of these are 100%, meaning there's no nine out of nine
或十分之十 前四頁有26個數字
or ten out of ten, and the first four pages have 26 numbers,
第五頁有27個 最后兩頁又是26個
the fifth has 27 and the last two have 26 again.
可能是巧合 只是信息的羅列方式
Could be an accident. Just the way the information's spaced.
看起來是刻意而為之的 每一頁都不滿
No, seems deliberate to me. None of these pages are full.
那一連串AM開頭的名字呢
What about the list of A.M. names?
沒有任何意義 我同意你們的看法 應該是化名
Means nothing to me. I agree with you guys. It's got to be an alias.
也許是對110小組懷恨在心的人
Maybe it's someone with a grudge against the 110th?
我們逮捕了很多人
We've arrested a lot of people.
詹姆斯巴爾呢
What about James Barr?
他技術高明 有神經質
I mean, that guy's got the skills and a screw loose.
巴爾是名射手 無法想象 他把人從直升機上扔下去的畫面
Barr's a shooter. Can't picture him throwing someone out of a helicopter.
我去年在印第安納州遇見了他
Plus, I ran into him in Indiana last year.
他現在欠我人情
He owes me now.
我不想知道
I don't want to know.
“松林荒原”
Pine Barrens.
大約有一百萬英畝
About a million lonely acres.
很像他們在紐約北部 發現弗朗茨尸體的地方
A lot like the spot Upstate New York where they found Franz.
他們把他破碎的尸體扔在那里 任其腐爛
They left his broken body out there to rot.
據我們所知 斯旺也在那里
For all we know, Swan's out there, too.
還有桑切斯和奧羅斯科
And Sanchez. And Orozco.
沒有布魯斯電臺嗎
There's no blues station?
兄弟 我們現在在澤西
Bro, we're in Jersey.
是我手機上的
It's from my phone.
以前你不在的時候 弗朗茨總是在總部大聲放這首歌
Franz used to blast this at HQ all the time when you weren't around.
放著吧
Leave it.
他們用假名字租了一輛車 但是是卡拉迪克森去租的
They rented a car under a fake name, but it's, uh, it's Karla Dixon.
她現在跟他們匯合了
She's with them now.
他們前往大西洋城 可能是去找他們的伙伴
They're headed towards Atlantic City, probably gonna try to find their missing buddies.
很好 一個地方 一網打盡
Good. All in the same place at once.
你到大西洋城以后 殺了他們
When you get there, take them out.
收到
Copy that.
你還記得我說過我需要支援嗎  我認識一些當地的人才
You remember what I said about needing backup? I know some local talent.
你需要誰 盡管帶上
Well, bring in whoever you need.
我們會付錢
We'll cover the tab.
我只希望你明天干掉他們
I just want them dead by tomorrow.
聽見了嗎 讓他們死翹翹
You hear me? Fucking dead.
新澤西州大西洋城
就像弗朗茨的辦公室一樣
Just like Franz's office.
還像我們的酒店房間
And our hotel rooms.
你說過他們洗劫了斯旺的住處
You said they hadn't trashed Swan's place.
- 是的 - 把那加入事物列表
Yup. Add that to the list of things
一定意味著什么
that must mean something.
你們知道奧羅斯科 會不帶打火機出門嗎
You guys ever know Orozco to go anywhere without his lighter?
美好時光
Better days.
只有我一個人沒有這張照片嗎
Am I the only one of us that doesn't have this photo?
- 我有 - 我有
- Got mine. - Got mine.
我的放在書架上
On my bookshelf.
家里沒有墻的話 很難把它掛墻上
Hard to hang a picture on your wall when you don't have walls.
我們在這里是浪費時間
We're wasting our time here.
我同意 我們有兇手想要的東西 所有值得找的東西
Agreed. We have what the killers want, and anything worth finding,
他們已經得手了
they already got.
接下來去哪兒
Where to next?
去一家酒吧
A bar.
看看桑切斯和這個女人的這些照片
Look at these photos of Sanchez and this woman.
- 五十歲以下的人誰還會裱照片啊  - 我們會
Who under 50 frames photos? We do.
除了110小組那張 你還有多少照片
Other than the 110th, how many photos you have at your house?
- 不多 - 但她的加了相框 所以她很重要
Not many. But she's framed, so she's important.
我們要去幸運酒吧
We're going to the Lucky Lounge.
幸運酒吧
不 你們倆待在這里
No. You two stay here.
你們倆看起來像警察
You both look like cops.
你們倆又像什么
What do you two look like?
《小姐與流浪漢》
Lady and the Tramp.
嘿 這個女人今天上班嗎
Hey. This woman working today?
你是誰
Who are you?
豪爾赫桑切斯的朋友
Friends of Jorge Sanchez.
嘿 杜爾斯
Hey, Dulls.
這倆說他們是桑切斯的朋友 想跟米萊娜談談
These guys say they're friends of Sanchez, want to talk to Milena.
帶他們去后面 她在記賬
Take them back to the office. She's doing the books.
米萊娜
Milena.
拿著你的東西 立刻離開這里
Take your shit and get out of here, now.
我知道他不一樣
I get that he's a different kind of guy,
但我們的指揮官居然買二手內衣
but our commanding officer buys used underwear.
- 那不是照片里的女孩嗎  - 媽的
Isn't that the girl from the photo? Oh, shit.
嘿
Hey!
我們就只能走到這里了
This is as far as we're going.
怎么回事 伙計們
What's going on, fellas?
別再來搞我們的朋友了
You guys are gonna stop coming around here and messing with our friends.
聽我說 朋友 你有點...
Look, pal, you somehow got...
別碰我
Don't touch me!
等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
走啊
Move your ass.
別再打了 我受夠了
I'm done, I'm done.
還好奧唐納和我沒進去
Well, it's a good thing O'Donnell and I didn't go in.
否則可能會出岔子
Something could've gone wrong.
你在交朋友嗎 大塊頭
You making friends, big fella?
抱歉 如果我知道你們是誰 就不會逃跑了
I'm so sorry. I never would've run if I'd known who you were.
我應該認出你們的 我在豪爾赫的照片里看到過你們
I should've recognized you from Jorge's photos.
我的朋友們只是想保護我
My guys were just looking out for me.
大約一周前 一個可怕的家伙 來這里問過她
Scary dude came in here asking for her about a week ago.
那家伙說他和桑切斯以及奧羅斯科 一起在做某個大型安全工作
Said he was working with Sanchez and Orozco on some big security job.
是個寬肩禿頂的家伙
Broad-shouldered bald guy?
不是 他有頭發
No. He had hair.
臉頰上有傷疤
Scar down his cheek.
他想知道桑切斯有沒有 留給我任何數字存儲設備
He wanted to know if Sanchez had left any kind of digital storage device with me.
我不知道他在說什么
I-I had no idea what he was talking about.
那家伙給我一種不祥的感覺 他一走 我就給豪爾赫打了電話
I got a bad vibe off the guy, so soon as he left, I called Jorge.
他沒接
He didn't answer.
他們之前也因為工作失聯過 但這次
They've gone dark before, part of the job, but this...
感覺不一樣
feels different.
你說你認識桑切斯
Then you come in, claiming to know Sanchez,
而你看起來像是被雇來的打手
looking like the kind of people somebody'd hire to rough someone up.
無意冒犯 我以為你不可信
No offense. Assumed you were bad news.
你知道桑切斯和奧羅斯科有沒有跟
Do you know if Sanchez and Orozco had any recent contact
卡爾文弗朗茨或托尼斯旺聯系嗎
with Calvin Franz or Tony Swan?
他幾周前來過 他們已經很久沒見面了
Actually, yeah. He was here a couple weeks ago. They hadn't seen each other in forever.
我給他們拍了張照
I took a picture of them.
他們當時在調查一起案子
They were working a case together.
- 桑切斯跟你說的  - 是的
Sanchez told you that? Yeah.
什么案子
What was it?
他沒提細節
He didn't mention details.
斯旺也參與了嗎
Was Swan involved?
他沒來大西洋城
He didn't come down to A.C.,
但我聽到他們提到了他的名字
but I heard them mention his name.
你們問過弗朗茨這件事嗎
You tried asking Franz about this?
- 我們問不了 - 為什么
- We can't. - Why not?
有人把他從直升機上扔了下去
Someone threw him out of a helicopter.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你們覺得豪爾赫 和曼努埃爾也死了嗎
You think Jorge and Manuel are dead, too?
我們還不知道
We don't know yet.
如果他們還活著 我們會找到他們 但我們需要你幫忙
If they're alive, we'll find them, but we need your help.
你還記得什么沒告訴我們的事情嗎
Is there anything else you can recall that you haven't told us?
我不知道
I don't know.
我上次看見豪爾赫時 他坐在那邊那張凳子上
Last time I saw Jorge, he was sitting on that stool right there.
他接了一個電話 似乎很重要
He got a call. Seemed important.
他說什么了
He say anything?
他重復了幾個數字 好像因此很驚訝
Kind of. He-he repeated a couple of numbers, kind of like he was surprised by them,
或者擔心
or-or worried, maybe.
他說他要出去 然后就再也沒回來
Then he said he was going out for a while, and he never came back.
- 你記得那些數字嗎  - 記得
Do you remember the numbers? Yeah.
他說
He said,
“六千五 每手十萬” 不知道是什么意思
"650 at 100k each." No idea what he meant by that.
- 你確定  - 非常確定
You're sure that's what he said? I'm positive.
他說:“六千五 每手十萬”
He said, "650 at 100k,"
他吻了我的臉頰 跑出了那扇門
he kissed me on the cheek and he ran out that door.
你會記得你愛的人 對你說的最后一句話
You remember the last words someone you love said to you.
我們已經掌握了數字 有紐約車牌
We've got the numbers, we've got the New York plates.
也許這事與痛恨110小組的人無關
Maybe this isn't about someone with a grudge against the 110th.
我們中的四人很可能已經被殺害了
If you haven't noticed, it's pretty likely four of us have already been killed already.
米萊娜說弗朗茨幾周前來過這里
Milena said Franz was here a couple weeks ago.
如果某些事讓他們覺得 我們處于危險之中
If the guys were onto something that made them think we were all in danger,
那他們當時就會給我們打電話 而不是幾周后才打
they would've called then, not weeks later.
六千五 每手十萬 我們說的是六千五百萬美元
650 at 100k, we're talking 65 million bucks.
黑籌碼太多了
That's a lot of black chips.
大多數地方 不是這里
Most places. Not here.
大西洋城的賭場大量斂財 怎么
Atlantic City casinos rake in, what?
賭場的年總收入應該是幾十億
Gross gaming revenue's got to be a couple billion a year, easy.
六千五百萬 如果隨著時間的推移
65 million, if taken carefully, over time,
可能會被忽視一段時間
could go unnoticed for a while.
不會那么久 賭場會計會像老鷹一樣盯著
Not that long. Not with casino accountants watching the take like hawks.
有沒有可能是壞人將其藏得夠久
But could the bad guys hide it in the margins long enough to get away with it
在會計發現之前逃脫懲罰
before the calculator crew catches on?
桑切斯和奧羅斯科 是自由職業賭場保安
Sanchez and Orozco do freelance casino security.
也許事情是從他們開始的
I mean, maybe it all started with them.
他們偶然發現了一件大事 需要幫忙
They stumbled onto something big, they needed help...
所以他們聯系了弗朗茨 或許還有斯旺
So they reached out to Franz... maybe Swan.
這件事可能與賭博有關
Guess this whole thing could be tied to gaming.
我是艾莉 為你們服務 你們需要什么
I'm Ellie, I'll be your server. What can I get you?
我們找安全總監
The casino's director of security.
請立刻帶我們去吧
Now, please.
你們是110小組的
So, you're the 110th.
是我們組剩下的成員
What's left of us.
桑切斯和奧羅斯科總是提起你們
Sanchez and Orozco talk about you guys all the time.
請坐
Please.
你之前很了解他們嗎
So, you knew them well?
是的 他們會對木板人行道 所有賭場進行背景調查
Uh, yeah. They would do background checks for all the casinos on the boardwalk.
等等 你剛說:“之前了解”
Hold on. Uh, you just said "knew them."
過去時
Past tense.
我們認為他們可能已經死了
We have reason to believe they might be dead.
見鬼
Oh, shit.
我上個月在白宮三明治店 吃午餐的時候還見過他們
I-I just saw them, uh, while I was picking up lunch at White House Subs last month.
- 我能幫什么忙嗎  - 這些數據有什么意義嗎
How can I help? These numbers mean anything to you?
就這么看沒什么意義
Not offhand.
那“六千五 每手十萬”呢
What about the phrase, "650 at 100k each"?
不知道 這究竟是怎么回事
No. Uh, what's this all about?
桑切斯和奧羅斯科可能一直在調查
We think Sanchez and Orozco
一起價值六千五百萬的賭博騙局
may have been looking into a $65 million gambling scam.
好吧
Okay.
你們說的“六千五”可能是 被操縱的老虎機或固定手牌
Uh, well, in that case, your "650" could be rigged slot machines or fixed hands of poker,
但每手十萬 那可是相當高的賭注
but at 100k per hand, that'd be incredibly high stakes.
我現在就可以告訴你們 我們的賬都是對的
And I can tell you right now, our books are on mark.
一分錢都不少
All right? We're not missing a penny.
那你的競爭對手呢
What about your competitors?
我可以打聽一下
You know, I can... I can ask around,
看是否有人知道桑切斯 和奧羅斯科在調查什么案子
see if anyone knew what Sanchez and Orozco were working on.
- 那樣可能會縮小范圍 - 你打聽時 也順道查查這些名字
That might narrow it down for you. While you're at it, run these names,
看是否有人用其中的名字 登記入住酒店
see if any of them are registered at a hotel in town.
這可能要花幾個小時 你們住哪兒
Uh... you know, this-this might take a few hours. Where are you guys staying?
我們還不知道
Don't know yet.
那請讓我來安排吧
Well, then, please, allow me.
不需要
Not necessary.
那不行 你們可是 桑切斯和奧羅斯科的朋友
No, no. Any friends of Sanchez and Orozco.
看來我們現在只有一間套房了
Well, it looks like all we have available is a suite.
我猜那也夠了吧
I guess that'll have to do.
跟我來 我會安排你們安頓下來
Come on, I'll get you guys settled in.
- 我們去住汽車旅館就行了 - 雷徹
We'll be fine at a motel. Reacher,
當有人請你免費住套房時 直接答應就好
when someone offers to comp you a suite, just say yes.
我們會讓他們送你 一張公園長椅 讓你睡覺
Yeah. We'll have them send you up a park bench to sleep on.
你會有賓至如歸的感覺
You'll feel right at home.
雷徹 你不會還想住汽車旅館吧
What was that about a motel, Reacher?
這地方肯定有水療中心
Whoa. I bet this place has a spa.
我要蒸桑拿
I'm gonna take a schvitz.
這還是個海景房
Ooh. Dibs on the ocean view.
奧唐納和內格利找到了吧臺
O'Donnell and Neagley found the bar.
里面“庫存”充足
It's fully stocked.
不過一會就不夠了 放好行李了嗎
Not for long. You unpacked?
好了
Yup.
我很多年沒住過 沒標榜“家庭友好”的酒店了
I haven't been in a hotel that wasn't advertised as "family friendly" in years.
我還是不敢相信 大衛奧唐納有孩子了
I still can't believe David O'Donnell procreated.
還是計劃生育
On purpose, anyway.
我記得某人曾吹噓說 唯一稱你為“爸爸”的人
Yeah, I seem to remember someone bragging that the only people that would call you Daddy
是跟你睡過的女人
were the women you slept with.
我現在還跟叫我“爸爸”的人一起睡
I still sleep with people who call me Daddy.
如果外面打雷 我還是跟三個一起睡
Sometimes all three of them if it's thundering outside.
你很快就會知道的 迪克森
You'll find out soon enough, Dixon.
- 你懷孕了  - 什么
You're pregnant? What?
沒有
No. Shit no.
她訂婚了 怎么 你不知道
No, she's engaged. What, you didn't know?
終于有人套住了我們的小母馬
Someone finally lassoed our little filly.
不
No,
我不知道
I, um, didn't...
關于訂婚那事 你們不必留時間過來了
Yeah. Well, about that, you guys can, uh, unsave the date.
好家伙 真的
Fuck. Seriously?
你了解我的 我一直是個數字女孩 一直都有人生計劃
Yeah, I mean, you know me. I've always been a numbers gal, always had a life plan.
計劃在一定的年齡 某一年結婚
Plan said to get married at a certain age, certain year.
然后 一天 我看到了他手機上的短信
And then one day, I see text messages on his phone.
說:“嘿 親愛的 等不及周五見面了
It says, "Hey, sweetheart, can't wait to see you Friday.
-“我愛你”等等 - 不是吧
I miss you." And all of that.
沒人能對迪克森不忠
No. No one steps out on Dixon.
顯然他也不行
Not even him, apparently.
短信是他即將來拜訪的侄女發的
Text messages were from his niece who was visiting.
但我發現當我以為他出軌時
But I realized that when I thought he was cheating,
我...
I was, uh...
我松了一口氣
I was relieved.
他是個很正直的人 我...
I mean, he's a decent man. I...
如果你要和某人共度一生
I don't know, if you're gonna spend the rest of your life with somebody,
難道你不想感受一些 舒服之外的東西嗎
don't you want to feel something more than comfort?
難道你不想覺得刺激
I mean, don't you want to feel excitement,
當你看見他時 有一點震動的感覺嗎
a little jolt of something when you see him?
有那么一刻 我以為 我會平靜且毫無內疚地擺脫婚姻
Anyways, you know, for a moment I thought I was gonna get out of it with no mess and no guilt,
但相反 我擺脫了婚姻...
but instead, I got out of it with...
卻非常混亂 滿滿的負罪感
A lot of mess and a whole lot of guilt.
答對了
Bingo.
這對你來說是好事
Good for you.
卡拉迪克森沒有安定下來
Karla Dixon doesn't settle.
謝謝
Thank you.
因此我接了臥底工作
That's actually why I took the undercover job.
花一點時間遠離這一切
Take a little time away from it all.
給我解釋一下 你怎么會同時當臥底和法務會計的
Explain to me how undercover work and forensic accounting go together?
首席執行官從德州一家公司 侵吞了數百萬美元
Well, um, CEO embezzling millions from a company down in Texas,
那里每個人都攜帶槍支 如果被逼到絕路 他絕對會用武器
where everybody's packing some kind of heat, and he was the kind of guy to use it if cornered,
所以除了數字分析之外 還有一點吸引力
so got a little intrigue along with the number-crunching.
好吧
All right.
你呢 內格利
And what about you, Neagley?
我每次查看領英網 都看到你升職了
Every time I check my LinkedIn, you're getting promoted again.
我過得很好
I'm having fun.
解決了大案子 現在帶團隊
On big cases, running a team now.
我之前試著 跟一家龐大的軟件公司簽合同
Trying to land this huge software company as a client.
我成功了 從那份值錢的合同里面收獲頗豐
I pull it off, I get a taste of that fat contract.
賺了不少錢啊
Making it rain.
我別無選擇 我想給我爸請全天候護理
No choice. I really want to get my dad on round-the-clock nursing care
給他租個離我近的房子 但那需要錢
and rent him a nice place closer to me, but that takes capital.
為什么要租呢 直接買下來
Why rent? Buy and build equity.
不 搞套公寓 合作社就是他媽的香蕉共和國
Get a condo. Co-ops are fucking banana republics.
是啊
Yeah.
你呢 大狗狗 幾乎音信全無
What about you, big dog? Being awfully quiet over there.
置業就像養蛇當寵物 或參加交際舞比賽
Home ownership is like keeping snakes as pets or ballroom dancing competitions.
如果你對此感興趣 那沒問題
Fine, if that's what you're into.
- 但我不喜歡 - 那你覺得穩定的工作有吸引力嗎
I just don't see the appeal. Or the appeal of a steady job.
企業界似乎跟軍隊也沒什么區別
Corporate world doesn't seem that different from the Army,
總感覺像是個牢籠
and that always felt a little like a cage.
只是不知道其他的事情
Just didn't know anything else.
我之前在酒吧里 有人演奏《狼嚎》
Then one day I was in a bar, and someone plays Howlin' Wolf
歌唱夜晚路過的火車
singing about trains going by in the night.
那聽起來像是真正的自由
That sounded like real freedom to me.
你像博科思卡爾威利一樣 跳上貨運列車
Are you jumping on freight trains like Boxcar Willie?
有時
Sometimes.
大多數時候 我坐公交車或搭便車
Mostly I take buses or hitchhike.
哪種瘋子才會讓世界上 塊頭最大的流浪漢上車啊
What kind of lunatic is picking up the world's biggest drifter?
- 他們很有意思 - 你在哪里吃飯
They can be interesting. Where do you eat?
我從窗臺上偷餡餅
I steal pie off windowsills.
- 我說真的 - 小飯館
I'm being serious. Diners.
有時讓我搭便車的人 會分享食物 跟我一起吃飯
Sometimes people who pick me up share a meal with me.
- 有時是我分享給他們 - 你睡哪兒
Sometimes I share with them. Where do you sleep?
大多數時候住在廉價汽車旅館里
Cheap motels mostly.
如果你找不到汽車旅館呢
And what if you can't find one?
停泊在碼頭的無人看管的船只 也很適合住一晚
Unattended boats in marinas are good for a night.
熄火的卡車的平板也適合
Flatbeds of parked trucks.
有一次 我在發現的吊床上 睡了個好覺
Had a great night's sleep in a hammock I spotted in some guy's backyard once
- 可惜灑水器澆滅了我的美夢 - 天啊
till the sprinklers went off. Good God, man.
- 你還真是一根棍和一塊布就走天下 - 行李太多了
All you need is a stick and a bindle. Too much luggage.
還有問題嗎
Any more questions?
有 只有一個
Yeah, just one.
你從來不覺得孤單嗎
Don't you ever get lonely?
任您吃自助餐
有人把標語當成個人挑戰了呀
Looks like someone took the sign as a personal challenge.
多琳 我只是在熱身
Doreen, I'm just warming up.
如果你喜歡晚餐 請務必試一下尼普頓的自助早餐
If you liked the dinner, make sure to try Neptune's breakfast buffet.
每天早上六點開始
Every day, starting at 6:00 a.m.
謝謝
Thank you.
看來我不是唯一一個睡不著的
Looks like I'm not the only one who couldn't sleep.
數字讓我放松
Numbers relax me.
如果我要做點數學計算 不如順便賺點錢 我要叫停
Figured if I was gonna do math, I might as well make some walking-around money. Stand.
你的兩只手上顯示的是十和八
Ma'am, you're showing ten and eight on two of your hands.
沒錯 我可以加倍下注 賭上一切換取更大的回報
That's right. And I could double down and risk it all for a potentially larger payout.
或者我也可以叫停 保證能獲勝
Or I could stand and have a guaranteed win
因為下一張牌亮牌時 你就輸光了
because the next card out of that shoe is gonna bust you.
我祖母曾經說 “不可人心不足蛇吞象”
My grandmother always said, pigs get fat, hogs get slaughtered.
她可不是蛇
She's no hog.
我不是蛇 所以我要叫停
I'm no hog, so I'm gonna stand.
如你所愿
As you wish.
十五
15...
太多了
Too many.
恭喜你 女士
Congratulations, ma'am.
你今晚非常幸運
You're having a very lucky night.
我們想請你去聽音樂會 慶祝一下
Maybe you'd like to celebrate with a concert on us?
- 謝謝 - 八十年代的女士們
Thank you. Ladies of the '80s.
黛比吉布森 蒂芙尼和泰勒戴恩 會表演她們最熱門的歌曲
Debbie Gibson, Tiffany, and Taylor Dane performing their biggest hits.
你可以趕上下半場
If you hurry, you can actually catch the second half.
但我玩得很開心
But I'm having fun.
我們知道你在算牌
Ma'am, we know you're counting cards.
用腦子算牌是合法的
Which isn't illegal if you do it in your head.
但鑒于你們的安全主管 好心給我們安排了一間套房
But seeing that your chief of security was kind enough to comp us a suite,
我就放你們一馬吧
I'll cut you some slack.
動動你的肌肉 把這些籌碼送到收銀窗口去
Want to use those muscles and help me carry these to the cashier window?
把這些票給穿著會員專用夾克的人
And you can give these tickets to the guy in the Members Only jacket.
他看起來很喜歡八十年代的女士
He looks like he would enjoy some '80s ladies.
謝謝你陪我
Thanks for coming with.
深夜散步總能讓我頭腦清醒
Late-night walks always clear my head,
我收到內格利發來說弗朗茨死了的 短信后 我的腦子就一直有點亂
and after the text I got from Neagley about Franz, my head's been kind of cloudy, you know?
是啊
Yeah.
我很驚訝你口袋里 裝著賭場賺來的那些錢還能散步
I'm surprised you can walk at all with all the casino's money in your pockets.
我猜法務會計會在稅款申報的時候 附上這一筆錢吧
Can I assume the forensic accountant's gonna declare that cash on her taxes?
那些騙子
Those crooks?
要是我能審計某人的話 那簡直是我夢想的工作
If there's anybody I could audit... Actually, it's kind of my dream job.
現在的工作滿足不了你嗎
Current gig doesn't give you your auditing fix?
不行 我正在抓一個 從億萬富翁那里偷錢的百萬富翁
No, I'm just busting millionaires from stealing from billionaires.
我想做的是追查 政府的腐敗和浪費行為
What I really want to do is go after government corruption and waste.
你以前在山姆大叔手下工作過
Oh, you used to work for Uncle Sam.
- 六百美元的坐便圈 - 沒錯
You know what I'm talking about. $600 toilet seats. Exactly.
如果稅收能被有效使用 我們可以修路和橋梁
I mean, if tax money was spent efficiently, honestly, we could fix roads and bridges
以及學校 我們可以幫助需要幫助的人
and schools. Like, we could help people who actually need help.
我們可以有所作為
We could make a difference.
你應該這么做
You should do it.
是啊
Yeah.
我考慮過自己成立非營利監督組織
Well, I looked into starting my own nonprofit watchdog group,
但啟動成本讓人望而卻步
but start-up costs are prohibitive.
第一步總是最難的
First step's always the hardest.
是的
Yeah.
這就是我們以前 從沒有發生過關系的原因嗎
Is that why, back in the day, you and I never happened?
第一步是最難的
First steps were the hardest?
你在酒店房間里喝了多少
How much did you drink back at the hotel room?
足夠我問你那個問題了
Enough to ask you that question.
快說 我以前給過你提示
I mean, come on, Reacher. It's not like I didn't drop any hints.
當時我是你的老大
I was your boss.
那樣做不對
It wouldn't have been right.
我等了好幾年才等到這個答案 不愧是你雷徹的作風
Wow. [sighs] Well, I waited years for that answer, and it's pure Reacher.
直接 誠實且有理有據
Direct, honest and well-reasoned.
我能再問你個問題嗎
So, can I ask you another question?
你想怎么對付那兩個跟蹤我們的人
What do you want to do about the two guys that are following us?
- 你什么時候發現的  - 我們離開賭場時就發現了
When'd you spot them? Ooh, when we left the casino.
我以為他們是看到我們兌的現金 想搶劫我們
Figure they saw us cashing out and now they're gonna try to rob us.
我本來也是這么想的
That's what I thought, too.
看見停在那邊
But see that car
- 有紐約臨時牌照的車了嗎  - 怎么了
parked up the street with the New York dealer tags? Yeah.
我們進城時 它在高速路上跟著我們
Pretty sure it was behind us on the expressway when we came into town.
我們經過它時 肯定會有個持槍的男人走出來
Also, pretty sure when we walk by it, a man with a gun will step out.
我們轉身逃跑時 我們身后的人 不會離得那么遠
Then, when we turn to run, the guys behind us won't be so far behind anymore.
計劃是什么
So what's the plan?
我們不會經過那輛車
We're not gonna walk by that car.
我說“走” 就翻過柵欄
On my "go," over the fence.
走
Go.
他媽的
Fuck.
走
Go, go.
好的 因為你打了那個警察 肯定會發布你的逮捕令
Okay, there's got to be a warrant out for you in New York for hitting that cop.
如果我們在住宅區開槍 警察就會被叫來 你會被關起來
We open fire in a residential area, cops get called, you get locked up.
我們別用槍
Let's do this without guns.
看起來他們也是這么想的
Looks like they have the same idea.
需要我幫你處理你負責的人嗎
Need help with yours?
我能處理
I'll manage.
該死 我們小時候 會把名字寫在混凝土里
Damn, Reacher. When we were kids, we just wrote our names in it.
是賭場里穿著會員專用夾克的男人
It's the Members Only jacket guy from the casino.
媽的 如果他們追殺我們 他們可能也會去追殺內格利和奧唐納
Oh, shit. If they went after us, they might go after Neagley and O'Donnell, too.
不會 他們一直等到我們離開 木板人行道才動手
No, they waited until we were off the boardwalk to make their move.
他們不會去 到處都是監控的繁忙的酒店
They're not gonna go into a busy hotel with cameras everywhere.
沒有身份證
No I.D.
我們搜一下這個混蛋的車
Let's search this asshole's car.
看起來有人做了功課
Looks like someone did their homework.
手機
Phone.
成了嗎
Is it done?
成是成了 就是跟你想的不一樣
Not in the way you expected.
你惹錯人了
You're fucking with the wrong guy, Reacher.
你應該知道你不會有好下場的
You should know that this doesn't end well for you.
那為什么是你聽起來在瑟瑟發抖
Then why are you the one that sounds scared?
- 我覺得我引起他的注意了 - 我們要追蹤號碼嗎
Think I got his attention. Should we trace the number?
這是一次性手機 剛才接電話那人也會用一次性手機
This is a burner. Guy on the other end will be using a burner, too.
臨時牌照是幽靈車牌 車牌號已經被刮掉了
Dealer tags are most likely ghost plates, VIN's been scratched off.
沒什么能指認他們身份的東西
Nothing to I.D. any of them.
這些人都是專業殺手
These guys are pros.
我們應該留個活口的
We should've left one of them alive.
是啊 他們沒給我們很多選擇
Yeah, but they didn't give us much of a choice, did they?
也許沒有 現在我們的線索斷了
Maybe not. Now we have nothing to go on.
不一定
Not necessarily.
停車場通行證
Parking lot pass.
-“新時代科技” - 對
"New Age Technologies." Yeah.
昨天早上蓋的章
Stamped yesterday morning.
這就是你口中的線索
I think it's what you call a clue.
我們怎么處理尸體
Now what are we gonna do about those bodies?
我有個主意
I have an idea.
我口渴了
I'm thirsty.
想喝啤酒嗎
Want to get a beer?
新時代有什么發現嗎
Anything on New Age?
有
Yeah,
看起來新時代是一家航空航天公司
looks like New Age is an aerospace company.
跟大西洋城有聯系嗎
Any ties to Atlantic City?
我看沒有 它的總部設在紐約
Not that I can see. Headquarters are based in New York.
有一塊彈片打中我了 剛才太過刺激 我沒注意
Looks like a piece of shrapnel bit me. I didn't notice with all the adrenaline pumping.
幾乎沒傷到你
Barely winged you.
這里...
Here.
你在干什么
What you doing?
給傷口抹酒精很疼 我媽以前就這么做
What my mom used to do when the alcohol stung.
你可能只把細菌吹進去了
You know, you're probably just blowing germs into it.
可能吧 但感覺很好
Probably. But it feels good.
謝謝
Thanks.
不用謝
Welcome.
你知道 雷徹
You know, Reacher,
有時感覺孤單是很正常的
it's perfectly normal to be lonely sometimes.
任何人像你這么過日子都會孤單
Anyone living their life the way you do would.
今晚你不必孤單
But you don't have to be lonely tonight.
而且你也不再是我的老大了
And you're not my boss anymore.
科羅拉多州丹佛市外32公里處
所有六千五百萬都將裝在卡車里
All 650 will be in the truck.
你可以用我在車上 裝的GPS定位器追蹤
You can track the shipment with the GPS locater I paired to this.
路上至少標記了兩個好的伏擊點
There are at least two good ambush points marked on the route.
很好
Excellent.
我的人會處理剩下的事
My men will take care of the rest.
那武器呢
And the weapons?
都會在海外使用嗎 這是說好了的
They'll all be used overseas? I was told that was the deal.
那當然
Absolutely.
卡車司機不會受到傷害吧
And the, and the truck driver won't be harmed?
當然
Of course.
我永遠不會傷害任何人
I would never harm anyone.
- 早上好 迪克森 - 我們需要談談昨晚的事
Morning, Dixon. We need to talk to you about what happened last night.
整個酒店都聽到昨天的動靜了
Oh, the whole hotel heard what happened last night.
我就說你聲音很大
Told you you were loud.
這是昨天在從紐約就開始 跟蹤我們的車里找到的
Found this in a car that followed us down from New York yesterday.
司機怎么了
What happened to the driver?
他不會跟我們回去
He won't be following us back.
他的那兩個朋友也不會
Neither will his two friends.
媽的
Shit.
- 是誰  - 賴特
Who is it? Wright.
安全
Clear.
進來
Come on in.
你們看起來有點緊張啊
You, uh, you folks seem a little jumpy.
鑒于目前的情況 我不能怪你們
I mean, I don't blame you, given the circumstances.
我很討厭傳達更多壞消息 但我調查這些事情時
And I hate to be the bearer of more bad news, but when I was looking into things,
大西洋城警察局跟我說 他們在紐約北部發現了兩具尸體
Atlantic City PD told me that two more bodies have been discovered in Upstate New York,
就在他們發現你們朋友的地方附近
near where they found your other friend.
從分解情況來看 他們已經在那兒有段時間了
Judging by the decomposition, they'd been there a while.
我拿到了一份警察報告副本
Got a copy of the police report for you.
很容易借此識別其身份
Pretty easy to I.D. him with that.
他參軍時 他姐姐很害怕
When he joined the Army, his sister was terrified
他會傷痕累累地死去
he'd be killed with some disfiguring wounds.
她永遠不會知道發生了什么
She'd never know what happened to him.
就說他的兵牌可能被炸掉
Said his dog tags could be blown off.
為了安撫她 他在后背上 文了他的名字和服役編號
To calm her down, he got his name and service number tattooed across his back.
看起來很可笑
Looked ridiculous.
他不在乎
He didn't care.
他愛他的姐姐
He loved his sister.
我得給她打電話
I'm gonna have to call her.
我會告訴米萊娜豪爾赫的遭遇
I'll tell Milena about Jorge.
他們的傷口跟弗朗茨的吻合
Their wounds match Franzy's.
這意味著他受到了折磨 然后被扔下了直升機
Meaning he was tortured and tossed out of a helicopter.
還有一件事
Uh, one other thing.
沒有人用你給我的名字 登記入住任何酒店
Um, no one using any of the names you gave me have checked into any of the hotels in town.
我跟其他賭場的同行談過了
And I talked to my counterparts at the other casinos.
奧羅斯科和桑切斯 沒有替他們查任何案子
Orozco and Sanchez, they weren't working on anything for any of them.
我跟他們說六千五百萬的賭博騙局時
And when I told them about the $65 million gambling scam,
他們連夜查賬 我也是
they pulled their overnight audits. I did, too.
一切都在可接受的損失幅度中
Everything is within acceptable loss margins.
沒有人以任何一家賭場為目標
No one has hit any of the casinos.
你不必擔心
You don't have anything to worry about.
尸體都是在紐約發現的 跟蹤我們的車是從紐約來的
Bodies were found in New York, car that followed us was from New York.
是紐約的幽靈車牌和停車證件
New York ghost tags, New York parking pass.
這一直是紐約的案子
This has always been a New York case.
你要去哪里
Where the hell are you going?
我們需要更多的槍
We're gonna need more guns.
字幕翻譯:匡思穎
創意監督 朝思